A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004
The Library of Virginia
43092
29 cu. ft.
Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years. It may be necessary for an archivist to review any unprocessed, modern record collections (those collections less than 75 years old) that may contain confidential information before the records can be used by partons for research purposes or before any copies of records can be made for patrons. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for more details before planning your trip.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 12 February 2007
Biographical/Historical Information
The Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority was created by Act of Assembly on 15 April 1992 to lead the effort to design, finance, construct, own, and operate a baseball park for a Major League Baseball franchise in Virginia. The Authority consisted of nine members appointed by the governor, with each member serving a four-year term. Provisions were made for the Authority to appoint an Executive Director, acquire real estate, and issue bonds for various purposes. The first members of the Virginia Baseball Authority were appointed in 1995 by Governor George Allen. In 1997, the first and only executive director, Gabe Paul, Jr., was appointed. The Authority ceased operation in 2004 following the announcement of the relocation of a Major League Baseball team to the District of Columbia.
Scope and Content
This collection documents the activities of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority. The collection includes correspondence, reports, meeting minutes, press releases, videotapes, annual reports, and research materials. Correspondents include the Office of the Commissioner of Major League Baseball, various legislators on both the state and national levels, and local government officials.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series
Series I: Records of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority
Arranged as received.
Contents List
- Series I: Records of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004., Extent: 29 boxes; 29 cubic feet. (Box 1-29)
  Arranged as received.
  - Box 1.
    - Envelope: Cafritz Plan, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - VFB Payables, 2003 (Folder 2)
    - Expenses, 2003 (Folder 3)
    - Resolutions, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Conventional Wisdom, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Final report of the Jount Subcommittee studying Financing Options for the purpose of Constructing a Baseball Stadium in Virgina, H.D. 7, 1997 (Folder 6)
    - VBSA letterhead with logo, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Baseball tickets, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - United Securities Alliance: Rick Kowalick, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Virginians for Baseball Fan Club, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Kevin Appel, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - VFB Board of Directors, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - VFB Articles of Incorporation, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - VFB Budget, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Kevin Appel- Reimbursement, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - [no title], 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Loose materials, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - VFB Campaign Plan, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
  - Box 2.
    - Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Folder 1)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Folder 2)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Folder 3)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Box 3.
    - Citizens Advisory Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs Minutes, 2002 (Folder 2)
    - Box of Slides (55 slides) Miller Park, Wisconsin, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Contracts for Services, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Old Meeting Materials, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Meeting Data, 1996 (Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 2003 (Folder 8)
  - Box 4.
    - Envelope: LDA-LD Astorino/R.A.M. Stern, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Envelope: HOK, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - HOK Sport Activity, 2002 (Folder 3)
    - HOK Sport Ron Labinski/Earl Santee, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - HOK Sport Activity, 1998 (Folder 5)
    - HOK, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - HOK Invoices, 1998 (Folder 7)
    - HOK Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - HOK Contract, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - HOK Sport, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Goal Group: Proposal to the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Goal Group: Len Penna, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
  - Box 5.
    - McGuire Woods Y2000 Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - MWBB Y2K Agreement, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - [no title], 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Negotiation Session(s) Notes, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - MW Correspondence, 2001 (Folder 5)
    - MWNN Agreement, 1999 (Folder 6)
    - Lobbyist Disclosures, 1999 (Folder 7)
    - MWBB Correspondence, 1996 (Folder 8)
    - MWBB Correspondence, 1997 (Folder 9)
  - Box 6.
    - Major League Baseball Agreements, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Major League Baseball Office of the Commissioner, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - World Series, 2000 (Folder 3)
    - Major League Baseball Economic Data, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Team Valuations, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Sports Venues: Revenues and Values, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Baseball Executive Briefing, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - MLV Lawsuit, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Baseball Facts, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Attendance, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - FANS Antitrust, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Alan H. "Bud" Selig, Commission of Major League Baseball, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Contraction, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Anti-trust issues, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Revenue Sharing Article, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Naming Issues, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Taxes, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Stadium Financing, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - RFK Statium, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Virginia State Tax on Pro Athletes, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - PPEA, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Baseball Economics, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Patrick Kevin Brosnahan, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Loudoun Meals Tax, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Dan Snyder, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Norfolk Tides, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Bethesda Big Train Baseball Team, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - Seattle Pilots, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Prince William Cannons, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Nippon Ham Fighters, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - Design Competition, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Hampton Roads, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Carolina Baseball- Charlotte or Triad, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: County of Prince George, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Portland, Oregon, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Potenial Expansion Cities: EPG Site, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Mexico, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Ballpark Comparisons, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - Gabriel H. Paul, Sr., 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Sacramento, California, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: Vienna Metro/I-66, 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
    - Milwaukee Brewers Baseball, 1996-2004 (Folder 42)
    - Potential Expansion Cities: "Outside" site interest, 1996-2004 (Folder 43)
    - New Stadium Articles, 1996-2004 (Folder 44)
    - ABC Board, 1996-2004 (Folder 45)
    - Stadium and Arena Management, 1996-2004 (Folder 46)
    - Northern Virginia Population Study, 1996-2004 (Folder 47)
    - Goldman Sachs, 1996-2004 (Folder 48)
    - Stadium and Arena Financing News, 1996-2004 (Folder 49)
    - Prince William County, 1996-2004 (Folder 50)
    - Program Schedule, 1996-2004 (Folder 51)
    - Program, 1996-2004 (Folder 52)
  - Box 7.
    - MZ Sports, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - HKS, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Morgan Keegan Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Morgan Keegan/Ron Tillett, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Ron Tillett - Morgan Keegan, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
  - Box 8.
    - Michael Frey Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Michael Frey, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - State of Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Talking Points, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Short Term Tasks, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Projected Administrative Expenses, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - David A. Bell, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Dr. Robert "Bob" Wright, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Todd Stottiemyer, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Shawn McLaughlin, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Board Member Questionnaire, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - John Herzberger, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Stephen A. Horton, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Jerry McAndres, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Nancy Eberhardt, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Oath of Office, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Board Profile: Confidential Working Papers, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Official Appointments, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Ballpark Financing Plan, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Board Memos, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - Special Meeting Requests, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Proposed Grassroots Budget, 2003 (Folder 22)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting Matrices, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Board Member Information, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Personal Data Questionnaire, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Biographies: Authority Members, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Baseball "Quips"/Cartoons/Articles, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - Meeting Change Option, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Ken Grove Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Bill Buck Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - Bob Dix Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - George Barton Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Tim Hecht, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - Patricia de L. Marvil Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Dave McWatters Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Stewart McKnight Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Mark Miner Roger Moody Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - Terry Orr Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - David Birtwistle, 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - Herb Morgan Resolution, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - All Star Game, 2002 (Folder 41)
    - All Star Game, 2003 (Folder 42)
    - All Star Game, 2004 (Folder 43)
  - Box 9.
    - William-Mullen, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Young DC, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Washington Business Journal, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Legislation, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meetings, 19 October 2000 (Folder 5)
    - Inside Pitch, 2000 (Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Press Releases, 2003 (Folder 8)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Press Kit, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Promotional Materials, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Study Commission, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Binder of Informational Material, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Annual Reports, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
  - Box 10.
    - Starkey Sports Consulting: Bob Starkey, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Bob Stein, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher and Flom, LLP, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Summerfest, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Susan David International, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Souvenir Bats, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - SMA Services, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - SMA, 2004 (Folder 8)
    - Sun Newspapers, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - SCG Construction: Paul Franks, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Jan Stenerud, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - General Stadium News, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - SDS: Schneiders/Della Volpe/Schulman, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Stadium Advertising/Naming Rights, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Scanners, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Sign-A-Rama, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Stada.net, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Rachel M. Schlesinger Concert Hall at NOVA-Alexandria Campus, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - SW Franks Construction, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Team Services, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - TIME Copy Authorization, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - TV Worldwide, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Turner Construction, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Tulane University, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Target Marketing, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Team Marketing Report, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Takenaka Architects, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - Turner, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - United Airlines, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Uniglobe Travel, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - Virginia Commerce Bank, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Vanderweil Engineers, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Virginia Peanuts, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - Visual Landscape Interpreting, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Venus Services, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - VHB Larry Wellford, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Williams Mullen, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - Washington Gas, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - Wesley LLC, 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - WCUM TV Doug Joiner, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - Phil Wood, 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
    - Walsh Colucci, 1996-2004 (Folder 42)
    - YMCA of Reston, 1996-2004 (Folder 43)
    - Gordon Wood, 1996-2004 (Folder 44)
    - Wisc. Ballpark Dist., 1996-2004 (Folder 45)
  - Box 11.
    - Support for Baseball in Virginia, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - VA Marketing Study, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Community Interest, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Grassroots Support, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Prologue Development Group: Carl Sell, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Fairfax Bar Association, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Freedom of Information Requests, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1999 (Folder 8)
    - Community Interest Correspondence, 1996 (Folder 9)
    - Employment Interest, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - All Star Game: Coors Field, Denver CO, 1998 (Folder 11)
    - All Star Game: Boston, 1999 (Folder 12)
    - MLS Relocation News, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - New Ballpark Facts, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Major League Alumni Marketing, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Major League Baseball Players Alumni, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Major League Baseball News, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Freedom of Information/Copy Costs, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Freedom of Information Study, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Bid List Requests, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - ADA and Sports, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Campaign Finance Disclosure Act, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - American League, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Major League Baseball Presentations, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Major League Baseball Government Relations: Alan Sobba, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Major League Baseball Curt Flood Act, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - Major League Alumni Marketing, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Corey Busch, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Major League Baseball Players Association: Don Fehr, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - George Mason University - Professor Fuller, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - George Mason University - Professor Fuller, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Ballyard Design, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - VIrginians for Baseball: Rick Lowalick, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Incoming Nasty-Grams, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Press Conference: Baltimore Impact Study, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Merrily Pierce Confidential, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - General Interest Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - Ada Saslow, 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - Marcia Dykes, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - Letters, 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
  - Box 12.
    - "Impact of a New Major League Baseball Team in Northern Virginia on the Baltimore Orioles". Goal Group Consulting, LLS; Kagan Media Appraisals, Inc.; Penn, Schoen and Berland Associates, Inc., 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - CC and PR Committee Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Approved Leases, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - William P. Robinson, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Congressional Briefing, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Returning Delegates, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Senators, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - New Delegates, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Design Competition, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - [untitled], 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - [untitled], 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth- Conflict of Interest Filing, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Virginia Lottery: Penny Kyle, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Virginia Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Office of the Attorney General, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Conflict of Interest Filings: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2002 (Folder 17)
    - Contact List, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Legislation Affecting the Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - News Stories, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - Vince Callahan, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - State Tax Commissioner, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - W.W. Clement, Secretary of Transportation, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Attorney General Jerry Kilgore, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - General Assembly Legislative Action, 1999 (Folder 25)
    - Resolutions, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Mayor Fraim- Norfolk, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - David Prebut, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Virginia Department of Treasury, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Virginia State Government Organization Chart, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - General Assembly Action Baseball, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Local Delegation Letters, October 1993 (Folder 32)
    - General Assembly Letters, June 2004 (Folder 33)
  - Box 13.
    - Regular Meeting(s), 10 December 1997 (Folder 1)
    - Meeting Notes, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Meetings, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Meeting Notes, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Meeting Agendas, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Strategic Planning Session, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 11 February 1998 (Folder 7)
    - CC and PR Meeting, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting, 28 April 1998 (Folder 9)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting Notes, 21 May 1998 (Folder 10)
    - CC and PR Information and Meeting Data, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting Notes, 20 August 1998 (Folder 12)
    - Meeting Notes, 17 September 1998 (Folder 13)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting, 16 July 1998 (Folder 14)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Lease Schedule, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Governors Conference, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, August 1998 (Folder 16)
    - F and A Committee Meeting, 6 May 1999 (Folder 17)
    - Authority Meeting, 20 May 1999 (Folder 18)
    - CCPR and GL Meeting, 20 May 1999 (Folder 19)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Meeting, 3 February 2000 (Folder 20)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meetings, 1 April 1999 (Folder 21)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting Notes, 21 October 1999 (Folder 22)
    - Strategic Planning, 1999 (Folder 23)
    - Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Financial Information, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Meeting Notes, 18 May 2000 (Folder 27)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meetings, 6 July 2000 (Folder 28)
    - Authority Meeting, January 2003 (Folder 29)
    - Meeting Notes, 24 July 2003 (Folder 30)
    - Strategic Planning, 2002 (Folder 31)
    - Holiday Card, 2002 (Folder 32)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meetings, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Strategic Planning, 2003 (Folder 34)
    - Authority, P/A, 10 December 2003 (Folder 35)
    - Meeting Matrices, 2004 (Folder 36)
  - Box 14.
    - Box of Business Cards, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Early Site Selection: Site Correspondence, 1996 (Folder 2)
    - Early Site Selection: Site Submission/Site Selection, 1996 (Folder 3)
    - Early Site Selection: Site Selection RFPs, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - VHS Tape: Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Architectural Presentation, HKS, 24 July 2002 (Folder 5)
    - VHS Tape: Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Architectural Presentation, CDFM2, 23 July 2002 (Folder 6)
    - VHS Tape: Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Architectural Presentation, HOK Sport, 18 July 2002 (Folder 7)
    - Proposal Virginia's Ballpark at Diamond Lake. Diamond Lake Association, LLC; Torti Gallas and Partners, April 2004 (Folder 8)
    - Zoning, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - A and E Short List: HOK, HKS, CDFM2; LDA/Stern, 2002 (Folder 10)
  - Box 15.
    - Newman and Associates, 1996-2004
    - NOVA Roundtable, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Norton Utilities, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - NAIOP, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Nashville, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Oliver and Oliver, PC, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Millenium Bank, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Legg Mason, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - NATS News, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - News Channel 8, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Payne Webber Inc., 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Office Depot, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - PALM Warranty Information, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Paul and Singer, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Parsons Brinkerhoff, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Pelton Marsh Kinsella, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Printers, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Paine Webber, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Partitioning Hard Drives, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - Property Funding Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Pritchard Sports Entertainment Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Property Funding Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Randstad/Temporary Service, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Rooney Brothers Company, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Reson Design Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - R.L. Travers and Associates, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - RS Information Systems, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Ritz Carlton- Tysons, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Site Blauvelt Engineers, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - Ryan McGinn- Articles, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Smith Barney, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - SMA, 2003 (Folder 33)
    - SMA, 2004 (Folder 34)
    - Sport Service, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Solomon Smith Barney, 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
  - Box 16.
    - Accension, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - A and E RFP Legal Ad, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - ABC Builders, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - All-Star Game, 2000 (Folder 4)
    - Adaptive Engineering, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - AMTRAK, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Arthur Andersen, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Ace Movers Atlas Van Lines, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Act! Productions, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Aramark, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Adobe Acrobat, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - IKON Copier Division, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - AMPAC Mikio Matsubayashi, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Bid Candidates, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - American Seating, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Office Appliances, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Barton Turner Malow, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - BB and T, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Bob Johnson- BET, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Billionaires Club, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - BizJournals.com, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - The Bigelow Companies, Inc., 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Ballyard Design Holiday Card, 2001 (Folder 23)
    - The Bonham Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Brookings Institute, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Baseball on the Internet, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Bean, Kinney and Korman, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - The Brookings Institution, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Better Business Bureau, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - The Bond Buyer, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - CIT, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Caruthers Cord, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - CIT, 2000-2001 (Folder 33)
    - Charles E. Smith Company, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)